prospectivedoctor.com 2013-04-06

# Privacy Policy

**Why do we collect information?**

ProspectiveDoctor strives to provide the highest quality content and resources for our users. All information we collect is used to better our service to you. We make every effort to protect your privacy. No personal information is ever sold or released to any third parties unless approved by you or required by law.

**Information Collected at Registration**

When you register with ProspectiveDoctor, we ask for certain types of personal information. This includes your name, your birthdate, your current status, and your email address. Again, the reason we collect this information is to better serve you. 

First, we collect this information to validate all of our members. We want to create a positive and educational community which consists of contributing members and not spammers or artificial intelligence. In addition, we need to verify that all our users are 13 or over. We make every effort to protect the privacy of young children. If we discover that someone under the age of 13 has received membership, we will delete his or her account immediately. 

Secondly, we collect this information so that we can personalize your experience. With the information we collect, we believe that we can better provide you with content that will better meet your needs. No information will ever be given to third parties unless it is at your approval or required by law. We may also contact you through the email address provided for information regarding your account or for your routine subscriptions.

**Information Collected through Cookies**

ProspectiveDoctor uses cookies. A cookie is a small file which asks authorization to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps us analyze web traffic and can also let you know when you have visited a site. Cookies can help you better use the internet by personalizing your experience. They do this by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We may use cookies to identify which pages are being used on our website. This research helps us understand what resources are useful and what resources are not working. This helps us present content that is most likely useful for you. We only use this material for analysis purposes and then the files are removed. 

Again, all information we collect on ProspectiveDoctor is to help provide better service to you; this applies even for our website’s cookies. A cookie does not give us information about your computer or about your personal information. If you prefer not to use cookies, most web browsers have an option to turn it off. However, note that this may limit the usefulness of our website.

**Ads by GoogleAdsense**

ProspectiveDoctor participates in an advertising program hosted by Google called Adsense. Google uses a DoubleClick DART cookie in the Google ads served on prospectivedoctor.com. When a guest visits prospectivedoctor.com and either views or clicks on a Google ad, a cookie may be dropped on the user’s browser. The purpose of this cookie is to help better serve the users and guests of ProspectiveDoctor. Google uses these cookies to serve ads based on prior visits to ProspectiveDoctor and other sites on the internet. Users can disable the use of the cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page.](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/)

**Other Links and Advertisements**

ProspectiveDoctor may have content or advertisements that links to another website. We have no control over the privacy policy set forth by other websites. It is your responsibility to read and understand their privacy policy. ProspectiveDoctor is not responsible for any unwanted information that may have been collected from a website that was linked on our website. 

The same principal applies to advertisements. ProspectiveDoctor uses advertisements to continue to provide free services to you. If you click on an advertisement, we are not responsible for any information that may have been collected through the advertiser’s website.

**Information on ASK!**

ProspectiveDoctor has an ASK! feature to create a positive and educational community. It is your responsibility to not post personal information you do not want released. Posts on forums are made public so you need to take caution before releasing any information. We are not responsible for any personal information you may submit on our ASK! feautre.

**Security**

The protection of your privacy is extremely important to us. We take great efforts to ensure that our website is safe and secure for you. If you have any questions or concerns about your privacy, please do not hesitate to contact us at [contactus@prospectivedoctor.com](mailto:contactus@prospectivedoctor.com)[.](mailto:%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20var%20prefix%20=%20'ma'%20+%20'il'%20+%20'to';%20var%20path%20=%20'hr'%20+%20'ef'%20+%20'=';%20var%20addy53938%20=%20'contactus'%20+%20'@';%20addy53938%20=%20addy53938%20+%20'prospectivedoctor'%20+%20'.'%20+%20'com';%20document.write\('%3Ca%20'%20+%20path%20+%20'\\''%20+%20prefix%20+%20':'%20+%20addy53938%20+%20'\\'%3E'\);%20document.write\(addy53938\);%20document.write\('%3C\\/a%3E'\);%20//--%3E\\n%20%3C/script%3E%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3Cspan%20style=\\'display:%20none;\\'%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3EThis%20email%20address%20is%20being%20protected%20from%20spambots.%20You%20need%20JavaScript%20enabled%20to%20view%20it.%20%3Cscript%20type='text/javascript'%3E%20%3C!--%20document.write\('%3C/'\);%20document.write\('span%3E'\);%20//--%3E%20%3C/script%3E)

**Changes to Policy**

ProspectiveDoctor reserves the right to change our privacy policy by updating this page at any time. You might want to check this page every so often to see if there are any changes to our privacy policy.
